TOPIC
    about_EWSModule

SHORT DESCRIPTION
    A dead simple Exchange Web Services PowerShell Module.

LONG DESCRIPTION
    A detailed, full description of the subject or purpose of the module.

EXAMPLES
    Examples of how to use the module or how the subject feature works in practice.

KEYWORDS
    Terms or titles on which you might expect your users to search for the information in this topic.

SEE ALSO
    Text-only references for further reading. Hyperlinks cannot work in the Windows PowerShell console.
